antacids kelly in jail companies lennar
dot com today we had a really i think as
you do you feel it's going to be ten
minutes long at ten exercises we're
going to be doing fifty seconds acting
with ten seconds reston really quick
transition time in eastern europe are
you now
our first exercises me the flutter kick
cruncher redoing this for fifty seconds
on in ten seconds of rest
and you know we have a ten seconds to
move on seven x exercise really go to
one round each
who's going to start a flirt a crunch
and five
for
three
to you
one and startup
stickiness feed back and forth
we get that leg over top your body to
crunch up towards a foot out past that
way
it's tight as you can get a nice tight
squeeze another dial muscles point of
oakland down through just fine
the main thing is you watch those lines
open
just nice low controlled motions
you're not really keeping those legs
back and forth really fast you're nice
low swing back and forth
delegate drops down to as a ground you
wanna make sure it's covering off the
ground
and every single time he crunch up you
wanna make sure you keep the battle
lower back pressed into the matinee
trying it as much range of motion as you
can
just keep it going nice straight leg
gamepro geophys highs you can
poem about a banana five seconds left
wind and letter lax room route move on
to the recliner rose
so sitting up on the tail bone
lean back as far as couple you those
legs for balance
and startup
users muscles in those arms against each
other's that bicep in triceps
that chest manorama we are working
against themselves the entire time
c_-one push forward at the same time is
pulling back
keepers advice in tightening on make
sure that back it's perfectly straight
don't tell or background
remember the for the lean back the heart
of the two b
so the more you lean back the more you
have to keep those lays out in front of
you counterbalance your weight
an depending on how strong has
absolutely might actually be a we get
back further than those as can control
of those legs controls far scout arounds
she might need it even put in a way to
between his feet
she got a little bit longer
five
three
too
one and let a relaxing ten-second break
or moving on to a three polls took such
crunch next
so back down funny back
those lazy or straight above those hips
and startup
crush up towards those toes
three pulses mandarin liberal expect him
but don't let those ads completely
release you just dropping a short wave
back down
that pulls the top their range of motion
you want to be as high as you possibly
can you are really try to reach those
toes
jan point two billion back to adjust by
and costly trying to contract as a bill
muscles in
few let those muppet domo soldiers go
wherever they want to they're gonna
contract out
they're actually the forces a dull
muscles tube always be distended so
whenever you're doing a number of
donnell exercise you always want to
focus on point abba eban into your
sponsor connects them again
to train those muscles to go flat rather
push out
almost done
in five four
three
to you
one
and goin literal accident a full time
take a break here moving on to double
leg drops next
sos leah construed by those hips
and started out nice a slow drop it down
however this fee just love the gramm
free poem right back up
mistakes a lot of donnell control so if
that laura backs are slipping up on you
means is a little bit too hard for you
do suggest ben those knees
should change that uh... angle just a
little bit that leverage so should you
will be easier for you
otherwise you can let those fee
completely testing ground
benham a fully extended about five of
the head extend them straight up and
men drop from there
so doing a bent motion at the bottom
elisa hearts resort killers doing right
now which is a completely straight leg
dropping in straight down and point
right back up
there's a lot of hip flexor as well as
those logo muscles
they're moving to a side starred it next
gets few seconds left
five four
too
one government a relaxed yet ten-second
break to move on to that one
higgins aside starved etc
one and startup
drops that size our position dropping
the hip down i said well also in the
rear side
dropped out of it
get every summer time you come down
sides are position one of those
shoulders and those arms perpendicular
to the ground
here drop that have squeeze it back up
before use whichever a suicide
nice little motion also in back and
forth again she does a da muscles nice
in type the entire time
trade is much range of motion our belief
that you can if you drop a hit them
the lower back in as a da muscle should
be tense for support
stevedore a little bit longer
you get for your for liquid snacks
five
four
three
too
one and letter relaxed and move back on
sat back for those figures for leg
raises
wind and start about someone like ross
is a result the other
to make me a figure four on those legs
and one leg drops down to drop as low
you can we ground the coverage only
completely touched
before it all right back up again
steep halting back and forth the top of
switching which lays on top
begin those as need to be nice in tight
pullman billy budd introduce pine again
try to press the lower back flag is that
map the entire time
just keep those lines open berating
normally just make sure not hold my
breath
suzie cross that layover topper go
anywhere matured all that weight of that
leg drops onto the bottom lakeside
bottom legs lifting both
and then worry relax ten seconds rest
until we move on to those heel taps
three
too
one and stardom up
so crunching up
moving left to right getting into a
bully crunch as well and all crunch in
there
extra focus on moving osha was left to
right more than crunching your shoulder
four din across
so little bit of a crunch as well as a
rotation to that oblique trend of roldo
shows off down the one side
so version of a left hand that left foot
in the right hand and i write first
skewed emotion going into those lines
open door then pull down the spine
yep lake that's coming up next
and five for
too
one man letter lasted ten tickets
restaurant flip it over on sat stomach
first plank tips
somos elbows and toes
one and begin
just dropping a six left to right
try thought those hips to get to high
when you come back into the center
dropping off left to right nice low full
range of motion
try to go schiller is parallel to the
ground shes rocking that sits back and
forth to give a good torso twists as
well as an oblique and dhamma work on
this one
this is a huge range of motion
but try to get as full originals as you
possibly can begin trying to keep this
keeps up too high in the back there is
not only come to the center
just ten seconds left for moving to all
saying tote up snacks
five four
three
too
wind and letter relaxed at ten tickets
rested for those two attested and foot
back over onto your back
we were doing this for the table top
position so that means you're right
about that help
and started up
switching a c back and forth again all
saying one later time
nice low controlled motion that knee
stays locked in agar angle
ts all saying back and forth
two cans of da muscles pulled in that
lower back press kit that matched to
those lungs open
if you want to get a lot he's being with
us on this can be exhale that leg down
inhale a backup
exhale down inhale backup
gajski golfing back and forth to go zaps
nice in tight second belly button then
kills lines open
there just one more exercise you go
got about ten seconds left in this one
before we switch
to really folks are not letting them nhe
coming too close
one and letter relaxes your last rest
break lee et cetera moving on to plot is
hundreds necks
sustain that same position
back flight if that matt
and begin from socialism just a little
bit
achilles dumas harder versions here with
those legs extended out straight
nice full range of motion this just
which just slightly easier version of
that knee bent to the now you're a also
a table top position
if you want even easier to put this in
from this you can see what those feet
touched down to the ground
just keep them ocean-going
the for the drop this few ya from this
position of those legs straight
the harder scan again
who are nice full range of motion that
arm
from that need to get help
and pumping those hands
in time with your dreams of breeding in
five times fill in those lungs out
and excelling five times as those loans
are empty
ski picking on nice controlled motion
nice rigid arm sigma belly button then
almost done five
four
three
too
one and let relax good job this ab
workout is complete